https://www.quinssa.org.uk/join/privacy-policy/

Expand/collapse navigation
HomeJoin BenefitsPrivacy PolicyEvents Previous EventsAway TicketsEuropean TicketsMDSBuyActivities Academy SupportSupporter AwardsShooting Star CHASE AppealCommittee AimsConstitutionMinutes
HomeJoinEventsAway TicketsEuropean TicketsMDSBuyActivitiesCommittee
Privacy policy
This privacy policy sets out how Quinssa uses and protects any information that you give Quinssa when you use this
website.
Quinssa is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be
identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
Quinssa may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that
you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 25 May 2018.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name and address
contact information including email address
other information relevant to customer surveys
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the
following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
Send out regular emails advising you of Quinssa information, offers, merchandise, events and anything else we feel may be of interest to
members
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information
which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
Remind you that your renewal is due
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may
contact you by email, phone or mail.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place
suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note
that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such
sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate
that you do not want the information to be used by us for direct marketing purposes
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at members@quinssa.org.uk
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to
do so
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the General Data Protection Regulation 2018. If you would
like a copy of the information held on you please email members@quinssa.org.uk
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible at
the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
Quinssa GDPR Policies and ProceduresGDPR Policies and Procedures.pdf Adobe Acrobat document [277.0 KB]
BenefitsPrivacy Policy
Want to join us?
If you'd like to become a member, please visit the Join Quinssa page
Privacy Policy
Print
|
Sitemap
© Quinssa - Quins Supporters' Association - Harlequins Rugby
Login
Web ViewMobile View
Logout |
Edit page
